Hello, English learners.
你好，英语学习者。
Welcome back to EnglishPod.
欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
And my name is Katherine.
我是Katherine。
And today we're talking about something very serious.
今天我们要讨论一个非常严肃的话题。
Very serious.
非常严肃。
Today we're talking about capital punishment.
今天我们要讨论死刑。
So if you've never heard that phrase before, you might have heard another name for this
如果你以前没听过这个说法，你可能听过它的另一个名称
topic.
话题。
It's called the death penalty.
它叫做死刑。
Right.
对。
So if you commit a crime and basically the judge says that you will have to be put to
所以如果你犯了罪，基本上法官会判定你必须为那个罪行
death for that crime.
被处死。
All right.
好的。
So many countries no longer have this.
很多国家已经不再有这种法律了。
This law, the United States, you can see it in some places, some states, but not in others.
在美国，有些地方、有些州有，但其他州没有。
So what we're talking about today is the debate between to have the death penalty and to not
所以今天我们要讨论的是关于是否保留死刑的
have it.
辩论。
All right.
好的。
So we're going to actually have a little debate in the end of if we agree that we should have
所以我们最后会进行一个小辩论，讨论我们是否同意应该保留
the death penalty or not.
死刑。
But before that, why don't we listen to this dialogue for the first time?
但在此之前，我们先第一次听一下这段对话吧？
That's all for today's class.
今天的课就到这里。
We will continue our lecture on crime and punishment tomorrow.
明天我们会继续讲关于犯罪与惩罚的讲座。
Do you think we should be tougher on crime?
你觉得我们应该对犯罪更严厉吗？
Well, it depends on what you mean.
嗯，那要看你的意思了。
For example, we could bring back the death penalty for murder, give longer prison sentences
比如，我们可以恢复对谋杀罪的死刑，对较轻的罪行判更长的刑期，
for lesser offenses and lock up juvenile offenders.
并关押未成年罪犯。
Those sound like really draconian measures.
这些听起来真是严厉的措施。
Firstly, what do you do about miscarriages of justice if you've already put innocent
首先，如果你已经处死了无辜的人，那司法误判怎么办？
people to death?
You'd only use capital punishment if you were absolutely sure that you convicted the right
只有当你绝对确定你定罪的是正确的人时，
person.
才会使用死刑。
But there have been many cases of wrongful conviction where people have been imprisoned
但有很多冤假错案的例子，人们被监禁了
for many years.
很多年。
The authorities were sure at the time, but later it was shown that the evidence was unreliable.
当局当时很确定，但后来发现证据不可靠。
In some cases, it had been fabricated by the police.
有些情况下，证据是警察伪造的。
Well, no system of justice can be perfect, but surely there's a good case for longer
嗯，没有哪个司法系统是完美的，但肯定有理由用更长的
prison sentences to deter serious crime.
刑期来威慑严重犯罪。
I doubt whether they could act as an effective deterrent while the detection rate is so low.
我怀疑在破案率这么低的情况下，它们能否起到有效的威慑作用。
The best way to prevent crime is to convince people who commit it that they're going to
预防犯罪的最好方法是让犯罪者相信他们
be caught.
会被抓住。
It doesn't make sense to divert all your resources into the prison system.
把所有资源都投入到监狱系统是不明智的。
But if you detect more crimes, you'll still need prisons.
但如果你侦破更多犯罪，你仍然需要监狱。
In my reckoning, if we could lock up more juvenile criminals, they'd learn that they
依我看，如果我们能关押更多未成年罪犯，他们就会知道
can't get away with it.
不能逍遥法外。
Soft sentences will merely encourage them to do it again.
轻判只会鼓励他们再犯。
Yes, but remember that prisons are often schools for criminals.
是的，但记住监狱往往是罪犯的学校。
To remove crime from society, you really have to tackle its causes.
要消除社会上的犯罪，你必须真正解决其根源。
Well, if I were president, I would impose tougher laws and punishment.
嗯，如果我是总统，我会实施更严厉的法律和惩罚。
I would have a peaceful society based on fear of punishment, not consciousness of doing
我会建立一个基于对惩罚的恐惧、而不是基于做正确事情的意识
the right thing.
的和平社会。
You sound like a dictator.
你听起来像个独裁者。
Well, if it works, why not?
嗯，如果有效，为什么不行呢？
All right, so Marco, there's a lot of really great legal terms here, legal and crime terms.
好的，Marco，这里有很多很棒的法律术语，法律和犯罪术语。
And so let's look at a few of these in today's Language Takeaway.
所以让我们在今天的“语言要点”中看看其中的几个。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
All right, so let's take a look at the first one.
好的，让我们看看第一个。
They mentioned juvenile offenders.
他们提到了未成年罪犯。
All right, so let's look at these two words because, well, offender can be pretty general.
好的，让我们看看这两个词，因为“罪犯”这个词可以很宽泛。
It's someone who commits a crime.
它指的是犯罪的人。
So an offender.
所以是罪犯。
But we're talking about a special kind of offender.
但我们讨论的是一种特殊的罪犯。
Here we're talking about juvenile offenders.
这里我们说的是未成年罪犯。
So they're young offenders.
所以他们是年轻罪犯。
Right.
对。
In America, legally, you're a juvenile offender if you're under the age of 18.
在美国，法律上，如果你未满18岁，你就是未成年罪犯。
Okay, so if you commit a crime while you are a juvenile, you get judged differently, right?
好的，所以如果你在未成年时犯罪，你会受到不同的审判，对吧？
You don't get the same treatment as an adult.
你不会得到和成年人一样的待遇。
Right.
对。
Usually, the punishments are not as harsh because people like to think that younger
通常，惩罚不会那么严厉，因为人们喜欢认为年轻人、
people, younger children or teenagers, they don't really understand the law.
年幼的孩子或青少年，他们并不真正理解法律。
They don't really understand crime or good and bad.
他们并不真正理解犯罪或好坏。
So it should be easier on them.
所以应该对他们宽松一些。
All right, very good.
好的，非常好。
So we have juvenile offenders and we also have wrongful conviction.
所以我们有未成年罪犯，还有冤假错案。
All right, this is an uh-oh moment for a judge because a wrongful conviction, well, conviction
好的，这对法官来说是一个“哎呀”的时刻，因为冤假错案，首先“定罪”
first of all is a decision.
是一个决定。
So this is a court's decision on whether or not a person is guilty.
所以这是法院关于一个人是否有罪的决定。
So you convicted the person.
所以你给这个人定了罪。
Right.
对。
Marco was convicted guilty of stealing my computer.
Marco被判犯有偷我电脑的罪。
I was too.
我也是。
That happened.
那确实发生了。
Right.
对。
But it's a wrongful conviction if Marco didn't really steal a computer but we decided that
但如果Marco并没有真的偷电脑，而我们却认定他偷了，那就是冤假错案。
he did.
Okay.
好的。
So it was a wrong decision.
所以这是一个错误的决定。
Right.
对。
It was a bad decision in the sense that it's actually not what happened in reality.
从某种意义上说，这是一个糟糕的决定，因为它实际上不是现实中发生的事情。
A wrongful conviction.
冤假错案。
Very good.
非常好。
And actually related to a wrongful conviction, many times it happens because evidence is
实际上，与冤假错案相关的是，很多时候它发生是因为证据
fabricated by the police.
是警察伪造的。
Right.
对。
So this is a big no-no.
所以这是一个大忌。
This is something that really shouldn't happen and it's against the law in many countries.
这是不应该发生的事情，而且在很多国家是违法的。
So fabrication or to fabricate is to fake, to make something up.
所以“伪造”或“捏造”就是造假、编造。
And so evidence that's fabricated is evidence that the police or other people create to
所以伪造的证据是警察或其他人为试图让某人看起来有罪而创造的，
try and make someone look guilty but it's not actually evidence.
但它实际上不是证据。
It's not really.
它不是真的。
That's not true.
那不是真的。
It's not true.
它不是真的。
Right.
对。
And now moving on, they were talking about a deterrent for crime.
现在继续，他们谈到了犯罪的威慑。
Okay, so to deter is a verb.
好的，所以“威慑”是一个动词。
To deter means to try and get someone to not do something.
“威慑”的意思是试图让某人不去做某事。
All right.
好的。
So I'm going to try and deter my staff from taking early lunch breaks.
所以我要试图威慑我的员工不要提前吃午餐休息。
So I'm going to punish someone as a deterrent.
所以我要惩罚某人作为威慑。
As a deterrent.
作为威慑。
Okay.
好的。
So you have the verb deter and you have the noun a deterrent.
所以你有动词“威慑”和名词“威慑物”。
Right.
对。
Yeah.
是的。
And so oftentimes very strict laws are meant to be deterrents.
所以通常非常严格的法律旨在成为威慑物。
They're meant to keep people from doing bad things, from breaking the law.
它们旨在阻止人们做坏事、违法。
All right.
好的。
So for example, capital punishment is one of those deterrents.
所以例如，死刑就是其中一种威慑物。
If you kill somebody, then if you get caught, you are also going to be killed.
如果你杀了人，一旦被抓，你也会被处死。
So that means I'm never going to kill anyone because I don't want the law to decide that
所以这意味着我永远不会杀人，因为我不想让法律来决定
I'm going to get killed.
我会被处死。
Exactly.
没错。
And our last word for today, they were talking about imposing tougher laws.
今天我们最后一个词，他们讨论的是实施更严厉的法律。
I would impose tougher laws.
我会实施更严厉的法律。
Okay.
好的。
So to impose is a verb that means to put in place or to set up or enact.
所以“impose”是一个动词，意思是实施、设立或颁布。
And so...
那么...
You don't really impose, right?
你其实不是“强加”，对吧？
You don't really agree to do it.
你并不是真的同意去做。
Like the dictator imposes his will.
就像独裁者强加他的意志。
All right.
好吧。
So he makes everyone do what he wants.
所以他让每个人都按他的意愿行事。
But we can impose measures that do something.
但我们可以实施一些措施来达到某种效果。
It's kind of like forcibly making people follow some kind of rule or follow a person.
这有点像强制人们遵守某种规则或服从某个人。
Now sometimes you would see that you have a company or you have people at your house
有时候你会遇到这种情况，比如你开公司或者家里有客人，
and they're like, well, you know, stay over for dinner.
他们会说，嗯，留下来吃晚饭吧。
And they're like, oh, I wouldn't want to impose.
然后他们会说，哦，我不想打扰你。
All right.
好吧。
Well, I wouldn't want to bother you or I wouldn't want to create more work for you because,
嗯，我不想麻烦你，或者我不想给你增加更多工作，因为，
you know, when you're making food, you have all these people, they don't want to impose
你知道，当你做饭时，有这么多人，他们不想打扰
on you.
你。
All right.
好吧。
So that's another way of using this, impose on somebody.
所以这是这个词的另一种用法，“impose on somebody”。
All right.
好吧。
So after all of these words that we've taken a look at, why don't we start now with Fluency
那么，在看完所有这些词之后，我们为什么不开始进入“流利度
Builder?
构建”环节呢？
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建。
Okay.
好的。
So as you know, Fluency Builder is a place where we get to talk about some phrases and
如你所知，“流利度构建”是我们讨论一些短语和
words that allow you to be more fluent in English.
词汇的地方，这些能让你英语更流利。
So these are sometimes idioms or sometimes phrases, words that go together commonly.
所以这些有时是习语，有时是短语，或者常用搭配。
And the first one is no exception.
第一个也不例外。
It's a miscarriage.
是“miscarriage”。
So miscarriage of justice.
所以是“miscarriage of justice”。
All right.
好吧。
A miscarriage of justice.
司法不公。
Now we have different words here.
现在我们这里有不同的词。
The first one, miscarriage, it's usually related to a medical term.
第一个，“miscarriage”，通常与医学术语相关。
Right.
对。
It's a pregnancy.
是怀孕。
Well, it's a pregnancy that has a sad result.
嗯，是结果不幸的怀孕。
It's a pregnancy where the woman's baby dies or the woman loses the baby.
是孕妇胎儿死亡或流产的情况。
And a miscarriage of justice is a metaphor.
而“miscarriage of justice”是一个比喻。
It's a way to say that justice was not carried out.
是一种说法，表示正义没有得到伸张。
It means that, for example, with those wrongful convictions, the law failed.
意思是，例如，那些错判案件中，法律未能
To accomplish its objective.
实现其目标。
Yeah.
是的。
To accomplish its objective and to be fair.
实现其目标并做到公正。
Okay.
好的。
So a miscarriage of justice.
所以是“miscarriage of justice”。
Interesting.
有意思。
And moving on to our next phrase, they were talking and discussing this whole death penalty
接下来看下一个短语，他们讨论整个死刑
situation and she mentioned, in my reckoning.
情况时，她提到了“in my reckoning”。
All right.
好吧。
So this is a great way to share your opinion or your idea with someone.
所以这是分享你观点或想法的一个好方法。
You're saying pretty much, in my opinion, in my, according to me or, you know, the way
你基本上是在说，在我看来，根据我的想法，或者，你知道，
I'm thinking is this.
我是这么想的。
So I can also say, I reckon, right?
所以我也可以说“I reckon”，对吧？
Exactly.
没错。
I reckon it's going to rain later.
我觉得待会儿会下雨。
I think it's going to rain.
我认为会下雨。
So in my reckoning, in my opinion.
所以“in my reckoning”就是“在我看来”。
All right.
好吧。
I reckon.
我觉得。
And to finish off Fluency Builder, they said that the person or the criminal couldn't get
最后结束“流利度构建”，他们说那个人或罪犯不能
away with it.
逃脱惩罚。
All right.
好吧。
So this is another one of those phrases that each word maybe means something different.
所以这是另一个短语，每个词可能意思不同。
You can get somewhere.
你可以去某个地方。
But put together, to get away with something means to do something bad or illegal or that's
但组合起来，“to get away with something”意思是做坏事、违法或
not okay without getting caught.
不对的事而不被抓到。
Or being punished.
或者不受惩罚。
So you can say, get away with murder.
所以你可以说，“get away with murder”。
He got away with murder.
他杀人后逍遥法外。
You know, he did something that was really, really bad but no one caught him.
你知道，他做了非常非常坏的事，但没人抓到他。
And also it means the criminal got away so they couldn't catch him.
这也意味着罪犯逃跑了，所以他们抓不到他。
Or I could always say to my brother, he would always lie to my parents and get away with
或者我总可以对我的兄弟说，他总是对我父母撒谎，而且
it.
能蒙混过关。
So he never got caught.
所以他从未被抓到。
He never got punished.
他从未受罚。
Okay.
好的。
So he got away with his lie or got away, got his way.
所以他撒谎得逞了，或者得逞了。
All right.
好吧。
So I think this is an interesting phrase.
所以我认为这是一个有趣的短语。
Why don't we listen to a couple of more examples.
我们为什么不听几个更多的例子呢。
Example one.
例子一。
Do you think we could get away with using the cheaper product?
你觉得我们能用便宜的产品蒙混过关吗？
Example two.
例子二。
Thieves got away with two Picassos which were never found.
小偷盗走了两幅毕加索的画作，至今未被找到。
Example three.
例子三。
He almost got away with murder.
他差点杀人后逍遥法外。
Unfortunately for him, the police discovered his secret.
不幸的是，警察发现了他的秘密。
So we've taken a look at a lot of great phrases.
所以我们看了很多很棒的短语。
Why don't we listen to our dialogue for the last time and then we'll come back.
我们为什么不最后一次听我们的对话，然后再回来。
That's all for today's class.
今天的课就到这里。
We will continue our lecture on crime and punishment tomorrow.
明天我们将继续关于犯罪与惩罚的讲座。
Do you think we should be tougher on crime?
你认为我们应该对犯罪更严厉吗？
Well it depends on what you mean.
嗯，这取决于你什么意思。
For example, we could bring back the death penalty for murder, give longer prison sentences
例如，我们可以恢复对谋杀的死刑，对较轻的罪行判处更长的
for lesser offenses, and lock up juvenile offenders.
监禁，并关押少年犯。
Those sound like really draconian measures.
这些听起来真是严厉的措施。
Firstly, what do you do about miscarriages of justice if you've already put innocent
首先，如果你已经处死了无辜的人，你怎么处理司法不公
people to death?
的问题？
You'd only use capital punishment if you were absolutely sure that you convicted the right
只有当你绝对确定你定罪的是正确的人时，你才会使用
person.
死刑。
But there have been many cases of wrongful conviction where people have been imprisoned
但有很多错判案例，人们被监禁了
for many years.
很多年。
The authorities were sure at the time, but later it was shown that the evidence was unreliable.
当局当时很确定，但后来证明证据不可靠。
In some cases, it had been fabricated by the police.
在某些情况下，证据是警方捏造的。
Well, no system of justice can be perfect, but surely there's a good case for longer
嗯，没有哪个司法系统是完美的，但肯定有理由支持更长的
prison sentences to deter serious crime.
监禁刑期来威慑严重犯罪。
I doubt whether they could act as an effective deterrent while the detection rate is so low.
我怀疑在侦破率如此低的情况下，它们能否起到有效的威慑作用。
The best way to prevent crime is to convince people who commit it that they're going to
预防犯罪的最好方法是让犯罪者相信他们
be caught.
会被抓住。
It doesn't make sense to divert all your resources into the prison system.
把所有资源都投入到监狱系统是不明智的。
But if you detect more crimes, you'll still need prisons.
但如果你侦破更多犯罪，你仍然需要监狱。
In my reckoning, if we could lock up more juvenile criminals, they'd learn that they
依我看，如果我们能关押更多少年犯，他们就会学到
can't get away with it.
别想蒙混过关。
Soft sentences will merely encourage them to do it again.
轻判只会鼓励他们再犯。
Yes, but remember that prisons are often schools for criminals.
是的，但别忘了监狱往往是罪犯的学校。
To remove crime from society, you really have to tackle its causes.
要消除社会中的犯罪，必须从根本上解决其成因。
Well, if I were president, I would impose tougher laws and punishment.
嗯，如果我是总统，我会制定更严厉的法律和惩罚。
I would have a peaceful society based on fear of punishment, not consciousness of doing
我会建立一个基于对惩罚的恐惧、而非对做
the right thing.
正确事情的自觉的和平社会。
You sound like a dictator.
你听起来像个独裁者。
Well, if it works, why not?
嗯，如果管用，为什么不行呢？
All right, so now the big question, Catherine, do you agree with the death penalty?
好了，现在有个大问题，凯瑟琳，你同意死刑吗？
Oh, this is a big one, and I don't think we have enough time to go into it in much detail
哦，这是个重大问题，我觉得我们没有足够时间详细讨论
here, but I definitely think that is extreme, right?
但我觉得那确实太极端了，对吧？
And so we have this phrase, draconian measures.
所以我们有这个短语，“严苛措施”。
Right, they mentioned that in the dialogue.
对，他们在对话中提到了。
Yeah, so draconian, something that's draconian is excessive or severe, you know?
是的，draconian，意思是过度的或严厉的，你知道吧？
And I think that there are a lot of reasons not to have the death penalty, because the
我认为有很多理由反对死刑，因为
death penalty, well, you're pretty much saying we as a society think that murder is wrong,
死刑，基本上是在说我们社会认为谋杀是错误的，
but we're going to show you that you've done a wrong thing, like a bad thing that's against
但我们却要通过杀死你来证明你做了错事，一件违法的坏事。
the law by killing you.
All right, and so I have to disagree with that on a philosophical level.
好吧，所以我从哲学层面必须反对这一点。
But what about practical?
但实际层面呢？
Practically speaking, I think that there are a lot of problems with the prison system and
从实际来说，我认为美国的监狱系统和
the legal system in the United States, for example, because prisons are really crowded.
法律系统有很多问题，比如监狱非常拥挤。
1% of the American population is in prison.
美国人口的1%在监狱里。
And so I think that so long as the prison system still has problems, there's a really
所以我认为，只要监狱系统还有问题，
good argument for having the death penalty.
就有很好的理由支持死刑。
But still, I think that it's excessive and it's unnecessary and that there are other
但我仍然认为它过度且不必要，还有
ways to treat and punish prisoners.
其他对待和惩罚囚犯的方式。
It is an interesting topic because you have many different angles that are in favor or
这是个有趣的话题，因为从很多不同角度可以支持或
against the death penalty.
反对死刑。
For example, you have religious views where you say that you should not take a life of
比如，有宗教观点认为无论如何都不应
another person no matter what.
夺取他人生命。
Or you have other views that say that the death penalty is simply wrong and that you
或者有其他观点认为死刑本身就是错的，
can't right a wrong with another wrong.
不能用另一个错误来纠正一个错误。
Right, exactly.
对，没错。
So it kind of doesn't make sense.
所以这有点说不通。
But at the same time, you do, like you say, the prisons are full of people and it costs
但同时，就像你说的，监狱里人满为患，
around I think it's $12,000 a year per person to keep them in prison.
我记得每年关押一个人大约要花费12000美元。
So what do you do with all of these people that have life sentences that are going to
那么那些被判终身监禁、将在监狱里度过余生的人
spend the rest of their lives in jail?
该怎么办呢？
So it is interesting and many countries are very, very strict with their legal system
所以这很有趣，很多国家与美国的法律体系相比
in comparison with the United States, right?
非常非常严格，对吧？
Definitely, but there is a statistic that's pretty stunning that I think among the top
确实，但有一个相当惊人的统计数据，我认为在全球
20 developed nations in the world, I think only the United States is the one with the
前20个发达国家中，只有美国
death penalty.
保留死刑。
Exactly.
没错。
And actually, the ratio of people compared to the population that are in jail is much
实际上，美国在押人口占总人口的比例
higher in the United States than in other countries.
远高于其他国家。
That's true.
确实如此。
So it is a very questionable topic, but we want to know what you think.
所以这是个很有争议的话题，但我们想知道你的看法。
Do you think that the death penalty is a justifiable way to do justice?
你认为死刑是实现正义的合理方式吗？
Or do you think maybe it's just wrong and we shouldn't have it anymore?
还是你觉得它本身就是错的，应该废除？
Yeah, we're hoping that this will get the conversation going on our website.
是的，我们希望这能引发我们网站上的讨论。
If you have any opinions, please let us know about them.
如果你有任何意见，请告诉我们。
EnglishPod.com is the website and of course, you can always email us or send us a PM if
网站是EnglishPod.com，当然，如果你有点害羞，
you're a little bit shy.
也可以随时给我们发邮件或私信。
All right, so we'll see you guys there.
好了，我们到时候见。
Bye everyone.
大家再见。
Bye.
再见。